http://www.psychonomic.org/?page=legalnotice

PS Legal Notice - Psychonomic Society
Donate | Join/Renew | Print Page | Contact Us | Report Abuse | Sign In
Toggle navigationMENUAbout About, Mission, & HistoryBylawsStrategic PlanEthics & Code of ConductDiversity & Inclusion Task Force on Racial DiscriminationStatement on RacismElectionGovernanceCOVID-19 Working GroupCarbon Neutrality Task ForceFABBSStatistical GuidelinesStaffWebsite FAQsMembership Join NowFellowsPS Mailing ListMember DirectoryMeetings Annual Meeting 2020 Annual Meeting ProgramKeynote AddressSymposiaSpecial EventsAffiliate MeetingsRegistrationFamily Care GrantsMeeting AppExhibitors & SponsorsPress & MediaProgram CommitteeFuture MeetingsPast Meetings2019 Annual Meeting ProgramKeynote AddressSymposiaSpecial EventsAffiliate MeetingsRegistrationHotels & VenueFamily Care GrantsMeeting AppTravelExplore MontrealExhibitorsPress & MediaProgram CommitteeFuture MeetingsPast Meetings2018 Annual Meeting ProgramKeynote AddressSymposiaSpecial EventsAffiliate MeetingsMobile AppRegistrationHotels & VenueFamily Care GrantsTravelExplore New OrleansExhibits & SponsorsPress & Media2018 Program CommitteeFuture MeetingsPast Meetings2017 Annual Meeting ProgramSymposiaRegistrationKeynote AddressSpecial EventsAffiliate MeetingsMobile AppHotels and VenueFamily Care GrantsTravelExplore VancouverExhibitorsPress and MediaProgram Committee2016 Annual Meeting2015 Annual MeetingInternational Meeting 2018 - Amsterdam ProgramRegistrationSymposiaKeynote AddressesWorkshopSpecial EventsMobile AppAccommodationTravelFamily Care GrantsExplore AmsterdamExhibitorsPress and MediaScientific CommitteeCall for AbstractsCall for SymposiaFuture MeetingsPast MeetingsPast Keynote SpeakersJournals Publication Policies* Psychonomic Bulletin & Review* Memory & Cognition* Attention, Perception, & Psychophysics* Cognitive, Affective, & Behavioral Neuroscience* Learning & Behavior* Behavior Research Methods* Cognitive Research: Principles & Implications* Retired JournalsPrograms Leading Edge Workshops 2020 Workshop2018 Workshop2017 Workshop2016 Workshop2015 WorkshopCollaborative Symposium 2019 Collaborative Symposium2018 Collaborative Symposium2017 Collaborative Symposium2016 Collaborative SymposiumEstes FundNITOP SpeakersAwards Distinguished Leadership AwardBest Article AwardMid-Career AwardEarly Career AwardGraduate Conference AwardYates Student Conference AwardAccommodation AwardsPS/WICS Travel & Networking AwardNews/Resources Annual Timeline and DeadlinesFeatured ContentNewsletterPodcastObituariesPress & MediaStatistical GuidelinesCareer Center
Edit This Favorite
Name:
Category:
Share:
Yes
No, Keep Private
PS Legal Notice
Share
|
General Terms of Use
By accessing or using any of the Psychonomic Society (PS) Web site, you agree to comply with and be bound by these terms and conditions of use (Terms of Use). Please read these Terms of Use carefully as well as PS's Privacy Policy, which is incorporated herein by reference. If you do not agree with these Terms of Use, you must immediately terminate use of the PS Web site. These Terms of Use will take effect at the time you begin using the PS Web site. PS reserves the right, with or without notice, at any time and for any reason to deny you access to the PS Web site or any portion thereof, and to terminate these Terms of Use. If you violate any of these Terms of Use, your permission to use the Web site automatically terminates.
Indemnification; Applicable Law
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold PS, its officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors and suppliers harmless from and against any claims, actions or demands, liabilities and settlements, including without limitation, reasonable legal and accounting fees, resulting from, or alleged to result from, your violation of these Terms of Use.
You expressly agree that exclusive jurisdiction for any dispute with PS, or in any way relating to your use of the Web site, resides in the courts of the State of Wisconsin and you further agree and expressly consent to the exercise of personal jurisdiction in the courts of the State of Wisconsin in connection with any such dispute including any claim involving the Web site or PS or its affiliates, subsidiaries, employees, contractors, officers, directors, telecommunication providers and content providers.
These Terms of Use are governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of Wisconsin, without respect to its conflict of laws principles.
Severability
If any provision of these Terms of Use is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms of Use, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any of these Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or any other term or condition.
Copyright and Trademarks
All PS content, including the name and logo and all related product and service names ("PS Content") on this site is owned by PS, its licensors, sponsors, partners, content providers or other third parties and is protected by law including, but not limited to, United States copyright, trade secret, patent and trademark law. Reproduction, retransmission, distribution, sale, publication, broadcast, circulation, reprinting or dissemination of any PS Content is prohibited without the prior written permission from PS or other copyright owner if PS is not the owner. You may not alter, delete, obscure or conceal any copyright or other notices appearing on the PS Content, including any such notices appearing on any PS Content you are permitted to download, transmit, display, print or reproduce from PS Web sites. Any use of the PS Content not expressly permitted by these Terms of Use is a breach of these Terms of Use and may violate copyright, trademark, and other laws. PS Content and features are subject to change or termination without notice in the editorial discretion of PS. All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved to PS and its licensors.
Use of Content
Reproduction, retransmission, or reprinting of all or part of any PS Content found on this site is expressly prohibited, unless PS has expressly granted its prior consent to so reproduce, retransmit, or reprint the material. All other rights are reserved.
If you violate any of these Terms of Use, your permission to use the PS Content automatically terminates and you must immediately destroy any copies you have made of any portion of the PS Content.
Legal Disclaimers
Warranty Disclaimed
The use of the Web site and the PS Content is at your own risk. When using the Web site, information will be transmitted over a medium that may be beyond the control and jurisdiction of PS and its suppliers. Accordingly, PS assumes no liability for or relating to the delay, failure, interruption or corruption of any data or other information transmitted in connection with use of the Web site.
This Web site and the PS Content are provided on an "as is," "as available" basis. PS AND ITS LICENSORS AND SUPPLIERS, TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OR ANY WARRANTY ARISING FROM A COURSE OF DEALING, USAGE OR TRADE PRACTICE.
Disclaimer of Liability
Users assume all responsibility for the use of this Web site. Under no circumstances, including negligence, shall PS or anyone else involved in creating or maintaining this Web site be liable for any claim, loss, or damage (including, without limitation, DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL or CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, or LOST PROFITS of any kind whatsoever) in connection with, as a result of, or arising from the use or inability to use the Web site and/or any other Web sites that are linked to this site, including, but not limited to: (i) reliance by a member or visitor on any information obtained via the Web site; (ii) mistakes, omissions, interruptions, deletion of files, viruses, errors, defects, or any failure of performance, communications failure, theft, destruction or unauthorized access; ) any interruption in the availability of the Web site or PS Content; (iv) statements or conduct of any third party on the Web site; (iv) any other matter relating to the Web site. In states which do not allow some or all of the above limitations of liability, liability shall be limited to the greatest extent allowed by law.
Disclaimer of Endorsement
Reference to any product, service, hypertext link to a third party or other information by trade name, trademark, supplier or otherwise does not necessarily constitute or imply its endorsement, sponsorship or recommendation by PS. PS shall not be responsible for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the presence of such third party content. You shall be solely responsible for any correspondence or transactions with third parties.
PS Privacy Policy
See www.psychonomic.org/privatepolicy for more information.
This privacy policy applies to the PS Web site (www.psychonomic.org), together with all other Web sites operated by PS.
General Public
The portion of the PS Web site accessible to the general public will not expressly ask for information that personally identifies you or that allows the PS Web site to contact you.
Patient Information and Medical Disclaimer
Information posted on this Web site by PS should not be considered medical or psychological advice and is not intended to replace consultation or discussion with a licensed psychologist. It is very important that individuals with specific mental problems or questions consult with a psychiatrist, psychologist, or other health care professional. PS does not answer specific medical or mental health questions or offer referrals.
PS Members
The Psychonomic.org site requires you to provide certain personally identifiable information in order to use certain "Members" features and functions of the site. By providing such information, you consent to our collection and use of it, as described in this privacy policy.
The Members only portion of the PS Web site (Members site) will expressly ask for your Web site identification and your password to access the Members site. The information that you provide to PS to become a Member during the PS member registration or renewal process (including name, address, phone and payment information, together with any additional information you provide to PS and information regarding the manner in which you use your PS membership) will not be processed or disclosed by PS except as permitted by this policy or as required or allowed by applicable law or legal process.
This information will be used to process your order and if necessary, to contact you regarding the status of your order. You agree and acknowledge that your order may be processed, fulfilled or serviced by third parties other than PS and you understand that such third parties are not limited by PS in their use of the information provided to them to process, fulfill or service your order. Therefore, in order to process, fulfill or service your order, you expressly consent to our sharing your information with any necessary third parties.
The Psychonomic Society use your contact information to get in touch with you regarding the status of your membership, registration or any orders you may place, for instance. You may also be contacted by us or our agents regarding additional services and features, or we may request your feedback about your experience with psychonomic.org. We also reserve the right to make your contact information available to third parties whose products and services you may find useful. If you prefer that we do not use your contact information as described here, you may send us an email at any time to info@psychonomic.org.
PS may share your information with carefully selected and screened organizations, including other associations, educational institutions, government agencies, corporate members, etc. These other organizations are not bound by this privacy policy, and you should contact them directly for information on their use of your data.
Personal Information
PS is committed to protecting the privacy of its members, customers and the public and will collect no personal information from you unless you choose to provide that information. If you purchase an PS product online, we collect personal information required to support the purchase of products, including names, addresses and e-mail addresses. When existing demographic information in our database is incorrect or incomplete, that information will be updated. PS only shares your personal information when necessary to complete your order (for example, your credit card and billing information is shared with our bank for authorization, and your delivery address is shared with our fulfillment center and shipper).
PS sends e-mails to let you know about changes to its Web site and communicate with you about issues that matter to psychological science, but we do not sell e-mail addresses to third parties. (But see above regarding our possible sharing of your contact information with selected third parties.)
Visit Information
When you visit the PS Web site, the Society's tracking agent automatically collects some basic information about your computer, including the following: your most recently visited URL, IP address (your computer's unique signature), operating system and browser software.
The information collected reflects the user population as a whole rather than focusing on individuals. It is used to better understand the people who visit psychonomic.org. This information allows PS to identify the most popular pages on the Web site. Aggregated data of non-personally identifiable information may be disclosed to the PS Governing Board to inform them of the number and categories of people who have visited the Web site.
Cookies
The PS Web site sends all visitors a cookie (small computer file) that contains a unique serial number that recognizes repeat users and facilitates ongoing access to and use of the Web site. PS does not use cookies to monitor the use of its Web site by individual users. Cookies do not collect personally identifying information; they collect information related to the characteristics of your computer, or when and how you reached the psychonomic.org site. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. They do not pose a threat to a user's system or files. Each time our Web server receives a request for a page, it checks to see if the cookie is present; this enables us to determine how much of our traffic is from repeat visitors. We use this information only for purposes of planning and tracking, as well as assessing the technical function of our site. By understanding how our site is accessed, we can continually improve it to respond to user's interests. Please note that cookies are necessary to enable PS members to use PS's member only information on the psychonomic.org site.
Psychonomic.org reserves the right to perform statistical analyses and profiling of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform third parties of such information. Psychonomic.org will provide only aggregate data from these analyses to third parties; no personally identifiable information will be disclosed.
Security and E-commerce
While information is critical to our ability to provide high quality service to you, our most important asset is the trust that our visitors place in how we provide that service. Keeping visitor information secure, and using it only as our visitors would want us to, is a top priority for all of us at PS. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, PS has put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information collected online.
No Guarantee
Unfortunately, no information transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Accordingly, despite our efforts, PS cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.
Change of Policies
The Society may modify these policies at any time by posting revisions on psychonomic.org. Only the posted statement is effective with respect to current use of the site.
Contact Us
We invite your comments and questions about the psychonomic.org site, your experience with our site and services, and our privacy policy. Please contact us.
News
more
6 hours agoFABBS News Highlights: Oct 9, 2020
10/2/2020Society for Experimental Psychology and Cognitive Science Award for Best 2020 PS Poster
8735 W. Higgins Road, Suite 300 • Chicago, IL 60631 USA
Phone: +1 847-375-3696 • Fax: +1 847-375-6449 • Email: info@psychonomic.org
Use of Articles
Legal Notice
Privacy Policy
Association Management Software Powered by YourMembership  ::  Legal
